Contact

brandys6878@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/brandy-snipe-bsn-rn-ccrn-78627a36 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

BLS

Healthcare Management ICU

Brandy Snipe, BSN, RN, CCRN

RN IV at Memorial Hermann TMC Heart Transplant ICU Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Cardiovascular Intensive Care Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Customer Service, Wound Care, Cardiovascular ICU, and Medical-Surgical ICU. Strong healthcare services professional graduated from The University of Texas at Arlington.

Experience

Memorial Hermann Health System RN IV June 2018 - Present (2 years) Heart Transplant ICU

Bay Area Regional Medical Center ICU/CVICU RN Charge
June 2014 - May 2018 (4 years)

Clear Lake Regional Medical Center- HCA ICU- RN 1999 - 2014 (15 years)

Kelsey-Seybold Clinic RN June 2010 - June 2011 (1 year 1 month)

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington Bachelor of Nursing